Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Minneapolis Honeywell First in Controls The Story of Minneapolis-Honeywell, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Pinpoint Your Future With Honeywell, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: this is Honeywell, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Here's Honeywell, Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Honeywell World, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: The Honeywell World, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: The Honeywell World, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Collective Agreement between Honeywell Employee's Association and Honeywell Controls Limited, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Product Catalog for Honeywell Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Your Future Years, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Honeywell Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Personnel Directory, Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: a program for future security after you retire, Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: a program of medical care in case of illness or injury, Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Corporate Alumnus Program of Hooker Charitable Foundation, Inc., Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: a program of family protection if something serious happens to you, Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Hooker Chemical Corporation and Niagara Hooker Employees Union, Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Careers with Hooker, Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Annual Report To Employees Hooker Gas, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Hooker Chemical Corporation And Subsidiaries Annual Report, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Communications: Person-to-Person, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: Hooker Gas, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 6: Hill Top News, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Item 7: Sixteenth Annual Sales Conference, Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
    October 31. Item is in English.
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: From the Salt of the Earth The Story of Hooker Chemicals, Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Hooker Electrochemical Company and Niagara Hooker Employees Union, Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Program For Employees of Hooker Electrochemical Company, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Pension Plan For Employees of Hooker Electrochemical Company, Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Interview Information Blank, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Confidential Pre-Employment Interview Record, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 3: There's an Opportunity for you in Hooker Research, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Item 4: There's an Opportunity for you in the Hooker Electrochemical Company, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Encouraging Employees TO Further Their Education, Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunity With Geo A. Hormel & Co., Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Item 2: Trust Agreement For The Hotel Association Of New York City "A" Division Pension Fund, Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: The Corporate Director, Publication (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Statler Service Code, Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Item 2: Inside Statler, Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Employer-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Item 2: Employment In The Waldorf-Astoria, Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Hotpoint Headliner, Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Item 2: The Hotpoint Security Plan, Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Item 3: The Hotpoint Security Plan, Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Procedure Outline Hourly Rated Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Item 2: Hotpoint Shop Rules, Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Item 3: Welcome to Hotpoint, Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: The Houdaille-Hershey Corporation Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Employee's Manual, Publication (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Box: 23, folder: (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Teamwork In Action, Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Item 2: Teamword In Action, Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)